Guide to the Jennings Wood collection of Confederate imprints, 1862-1865 MS2127
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Jennings Wood collection of Confederate imprints
1862-1865
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Wood, Jennings
MS2127
2 Linear Feet
Collection consists of 328 Confederate imprints, most are pamphlet size or smaller. They cover a wide range of topics, but focus mostly on government and public records and laws. All are listed in "Confederate imprints", by M.L. Crandall (E483.C72). This collection is not a complete set.
Acquisition Information
Jennings Wood, a rare book dealer, donated the collection of Confederate imprints to the library in 1980.
Historical or Biographical Note
Jennings Wood, a rare book dealer, donated the collection of Confederate imprints to the library in 1980.
Collection Scope and Content
The collection consists of 328 Confederate imprints, most are pamphlet size or smaller. They cover a wide range of topics, but focus mostly on government and public records and laws. All are listed in "Confederate imprints", by M.L. Crandall (E483.C72). This collection is not a complete set; the Special Collections copy of the Crandall book is annotated to indicate which documents are in this collection. Please note: the original imprint numbers are used as item numbers, therefore the numbers are not in sequential numerical order.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Public records; Law; Confederate States of America; Imprints (Publishers' and printers' statements); Wood, Jennings
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  General note
  The statutes at large of the Confederate States of America, commencing with the first session of the first Congress; 1862. Carefully collated with the originals at Richmond. Edited by James M. Matthews, attorney at law, law clerk in the Department of Justice. To be continued annually. Richmond: R.M. Smith, Printer to Congress. 1862. Cover-title. 25 cm.%32882017975098
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  The statutes at large of the Confederate States of America, passed at the fourth session of the first Congress; 1863-1864 Richmond L R. M. Smith, Printer to Congress. 1864. Cover-title. 24 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  An act recognizing the existence of war between the United States and the Confederate States; and concerning letters of marque, prizes, and prize goods...Approved May 6th, 1861. [Montgomery 1861]. 4 p. 27 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 05/21/1861 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  An act relative to prisoners of war Approved May 21, 1861. [Montgomery, 1861]. 1 p. 25 l/2 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  An act to amend an act entitled "An act recognizing the existence of war between the United States and the Confederate States, and concerning letters of marque, prizes and prize goods, approved May 6th, one thousand eight hundred and sixty-one."Approved May 21, 1861. [Montgomery, 1861]. 1 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  An act to perpetuate testimony in cases of slaves abducted or harbored by the enemy, and of other property seized, wasted, or destroyed by them. no. 270 1 p. 27 cm. Richmond 1861
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  An act to organize forces to serve during the war. 6 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  An act to amend the tax laws. 3 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  An act to diminish the number of exemptions and details 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  An act authorizing Secretary of the Treasury to borrow specie to be applied to the redemption and reduction of the currency; 1 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  Address of Congress to the people of the Confederate States. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  Report of the Joint select committee appointed to investigate the condition and treatment of prisoners of war. 17 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
  Report from the Joint Select Committe appointed to investigate the management of the Navy Department
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  Minority report of the Special committee to investigate the affairs of the Navy Department.[Richmond, 1863]. 3p. 22cm. (Bound with no. 89)
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  (Secret.) (Senate bill no. 11.) A bill to be entitled "An act to provide for the further issue of treasury notes, and for other purposes." 7 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  (Senate, no. 13) A bill to be entitled An act in relation to the public printing. 9 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  Letter from Gen. Wise. Headquarters 6th Military District, Department South Carolina, Georgia and Florida, January 3, 1864. To Hon. Jas. Lyons, John R. Chambliss and others, of the Virginia Delegation hi Congress, endorsing and enclosing the memorial of Generals Hardee, Stevenson and other officers, dated December 17th, 1863, from the "Army of Tennessee," respecting the army. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  (Senate bill, no.51.) A bill to provide supplies for the army and to prescribe the mode of making impressments. 5 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  (Senate bill, no. 109.) An act to amend an act entitled "An act to increase the efficiency of the army by employing free negroes and slaves in certain capacities", approved February 17th, 1864. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  (Senate bill, no.H9-Secret.)A bill to suspend the privilege of the writ of habeas corpus hi certain cases. 8 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  Amendment to Senate bill (S. 129) to provide for the employment of free negroes and slaves to work upon fortifications, and to perform other labor connected with the defences of the country. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  (Senate Bill, no. 16.) Joint resolution defining the position of the Confederate States, and declaring the determination of the Congress and the people thereof to prosecute the war till their independence is acknowledged. 4 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  (Senate bill, no. 129.) A bill to provide for the employment of free negroes and slaves to work upon fortifications and perform other labor connected with the defences of the country. [Richmond, 1864]. 6 p. 24cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  (Senate engrossed bill, no. 121.) A bill declaring the mode of ascertaining the value of the tithe deliverable to the government under the true construction of existing laws. [Richmond, 1865?] 2 p. 24 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  (Secret. Senate no 157.) A bill to provide for the appointment of a directing general of the armies of the Confederate States. [Richmond, 1865]. 1 p. 25 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  Resolution of the Legislature of the State of North Carolina in relation to the pay of disabled soldiers. Richmond, 1865. 1 p. 24 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 222)
  Resolution passed by the General Assembly of the State of Virginia, in relation to the Confederate States impressment laws. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1865
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 236)
  (No. 18-Secret.) Report of the Committee on Finance on the bill (H. R., 92) to tax, fund, and limit the currency. 12 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 252)
  A bill to be entitled An act to amend the existing acts for the exemption of persons from military service. 3 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 265)
  (House no. 4.)A bill to regulate the navigation of the Confederate States and to establish direct trade with foreign nations. 4 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 274)
  (House bill, no.4.) A bill to be entitled An act making appropriations for the executive, legislative and judicial expenses of the government for the month of December, eighteen hundred and sixty-two. 8 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 277)
  (House bill, no.5) A bill to be entitled An act making Confederate notes a legal tender and to prevent and punish extortion. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 278)
  (House.) Amendment. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 280)
  (House, no. 21) Joint resolutions expressing opinion of Congress in relation to the conduct of certain citizens of Louisiana within the lines, and in the presence of the enemy. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1862
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 281)
  (House, no. 24.) Resolutions endorsing the recent proclamation and order of the President on the subject of retaliation. 3 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 282)
  (House no. 25.)Joint resolutions on the pending war, and matters appertaining thereto. 7 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 283)
  (House bill, no. 8.)A bill to be entitled An act to amend an act entitled "An act to regulate the destruction of property under military necessity and to provide for the indemnity thereof." Approved the 17th day of March, 1862. 6 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 284)
  (House bill, no. 4.) A bill to be entitled An act to prohibit quartermasters and others from speculating. 2 p. 21 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 285)
  (House bill, no. 2.)A bill to be entitled An act to declare what persons shall be exempt from military service. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 287)
  Amendments [to a bill to be entitled An act to declare what persons shall be exempt from military service. [Richmond, 1863]. 8p. 22 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 288)
  (House bill, no. 12.) A bill to be entitled "An act to increase and strengthen the Army of the Confederate States." 3 p. 21 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 289)
  (House bill, no. 8.) A bill continuing in pay all discharged soldiers by reason of wounds and injuries received in the service. 3 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 296)
  (House bill no. 21.)A bill to be entitled An act to provide an export duty on cotton and tobacco exported form the Confederate States to the ports or in the ships of any foreign country which has not recognized the independence of the Confederate States. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 298)
  (House bill no. 8)Preamble and resolutions on the subject of taxes. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 304)
  Mr. Foster's amendment to bill to fund the currency. 3 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 305)
  (House no. .) A bill to be entitled An act in relation to substitutes in the army. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 308)
  (Secret.) Mr. Garaett's amendment to bill of the Senate "To provide for the further issue of treasury notes and for other purpose"2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 309)
  (House bill no. .) A bill regulating the granting furloughs and discharges in hospitals. 3 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 313)
  (House bill no. 3.) A bill to be entitled "An act to lay taxes for the common defense, and carry on the government of the Confederate States." 24 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 316)
  Amendment proposed by Mr. Kenner, from Committee on Ways and Means, to bill "to lay taxes for the common defense, and carry on the government of the Confederate States. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 318)
  (House bill no. ) A bill to establish a Nitre and Mining Bureau. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 319)
  Communication of G. Tochman, touching his memorial now before Congress. 3 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 320)
  (House, no. 1.) Joint resolutions on the subject of the war, and in regard to the free navigation of the Mississippi River. [Richmond, 1863]. 3p. 23 l/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 321)
  (House bill no. 27.)A bill to be entitled An act to provide for the payment of officers acting under temporary appointment from the commander of any department, corps, division or brigade. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 322)
  (House bill, no. 1.)A bill to be entitled An act to provide for keeping in repair the railroads of the Confederate States necessary for the transportation of troops and government supplies. [Richmond, 1863]. 2p. 24 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 324)
  (House bill no. 6.) A bill to regulate furloughs and discharges to soldiers in hospitals. Richmond, 1863. 3 p. 24 l/2 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 329)
  (House bill, no. .) A bill to be entitled An act to prevent trading with the enemy or with persons resident in the United States. 1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 334)
  (House of Representatives.) A bill to raise a tax for the support of the government. 1 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 336)
  (House of Representatives, no. 23. ) A bill to be entitled An act to permit the funding of certain treasury notes not now fundable. 1 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 339)
  (House of Representatives no.9)Resolution on finance. 2 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 342)
  (House bill, no. 15.) A bill to be entitled "An act to raise a revenue by direct taxation. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 346)
  (House bill, no. 11.)A bill to be entitled An act to amend an act entitled "An act to prevent fraud in the Quarteirmaster'Sjand Commissary's Departments, and the obtaining under false pretense transportation for private property," approved May 1st, [Richmond, 1863]. 3p. 24 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 347)
  (House bill, no. )A bill continuing in pay all discharged soldiers by reason of wounds and injures received hi the service. Richmond, 1863. 3 p. 23 cm
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 348)
  (House bill, no. .) A bill to be entitled An act to amend the law in relation to substitutes. Richmond, 1863. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 349)
  (House of Representatives, no. 7) Resolution directory to the Select Committee on Finance, 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 350)
  (House of Representatives no. 3) Suggestions for financial relief. 2 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 352)
  (House bill, no. 4.) A bill to prevent trading with the enemy. Richmond, 1863. 2 p.23 1/2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 354)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled An act to allow commissioned officers of the army rations and the privilege of purchasing clothing from the Quartermaster's Department. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 355)
  (House bill) A bill to be entitled An act to grant a special copyright to W. J. Harden and S. H. Gazelle, for Harden's Rifle and infantry tactics. 1 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 356)
  (House bill) A bill to be entitled An act to establish a Bureau of Foreign Supplies. 3 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 358)
  (House resolution.) Joint resolution for the relief of Major W. F. Haines. 1 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 360)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide for wounded and disabled officers and soldiers an asylum to be called "The Veteran Soldiers Home." 4 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 362)
  (House bill) A bill to provide for the reduction of the currency. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 366)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.) A bill to be entitled "An act to tax, fund, and limit the currency". 5 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1863
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 368)
  (House of Representatives.) A bill to be entitled An act repealing existing and regulating future, exemptions from military service. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 370)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.) Amendment by Mr. Swan. 4 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 371)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled An act to increase the efficiency of the army by the employment of free Negroes and slaves in certain capacities. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 375)
  (House bill) A bill to be entitled An act to increase the effective force of the "Provisional Army of the Confederate States." 3 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 376)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide additional compensation for the soldiers of the army of the Confederate States, and for the families of those who die in the service. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 378)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled "An act to make additional appropriations for the support of the government of the Confederate States of America, for the fiscal year ending June 30, 1864. 11 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 379)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.) Finance proposition. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 380)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.) Resolutions of instructions. 1 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 382)
  Resolutions expressive of the determination of Georgia to prosecute the present war with the utmost vigor and energy. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 384)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.) Mr. Chilton's amendments to the bill of the committee. 3 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 385)
  (House of Representatives.)Proposition of finance. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 386)
  (House bill.) Substitute of Mr. Boteler for Mr. Wilcox's bill. An act to provide for the payment of horses killed, captured, lost or permanently disabled in the Confederate States service. 2 p. 24 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 388)
  (House of Representatives-Secret session.)A bill to regulate the currency. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 390)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled "An act to provide payment for slaves impressed under state laws, and lost in the public service." 9 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 391)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled An act to suppress abuses in the Quartermaster and Commissary Department of the army. 9 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 393)
  (House of Representatives.) A bill to be entitled An act extending the privilege of purchasing clothing at government cost, to all persons in its employment, who have been discharged for (sic) the army on account of wounds received or disease contracted whilst in the service. 1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 398)
  (House bill.) A bill to be entitled An act to authorize the impressment of meat for the use of the army, under certain circumstances. 3 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 400)
  A bill to be entitled An act amendatory of an act entitled "An act to put an end to the exemption from military service of those who have heretofore furnished substitutes," approved January 5, 1864. 2 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 401)
  (House bill) A bill to be entitled An act supplemental to the several acts relating to military courts. 3 p. 23 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 409)
  (House of Representatives, no. 366.) A bill to be entitled "An act to provide means to carry on the government. 3 p. 25 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 412)
  (House bill.) A bill supplemental to the several acts in relation to public printing. 2 p. 24 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 413)
  Joint resolutions in reference to the treatment of colored troops. 4 p. 22 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 430)
  (House of Representatives, no. 101.) An act to provide for the safe custody, printing, publication and distribution of the laws, and to provide for the appointment of an additional clerk in the Department of Justice. 4 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 435)
  (House bill, no 93.) A bill to be entitled An act for the organization of the Bureau of Conscription, and the appointment of officers in said Bureau. 3 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 436)
  (House bill, no. 120.) A bill to be entitled An act to compensate Charles E. Stuart, Israel C. Owings and J. H. Taylor for the use of an improvement in instruments for sighting cannon. 1 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 437)
  (House bill, no. 121.) A bill to be entitled An act to provide for the settlement of certain matters of account growing out of purchases of property as alleged by the purchasers for the use of the government, by Payne & Co., in the State of Texas. 4 p. 23 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864